https://dawngibbins.com/cookie-policy-uk/

Cookie policy (UK) - Dawn Gibbins
info@thehealthyhappyhub.co.uk
FollowFollowFollowFollowFollow
HomeCookie policy (UK)
Shop
Cookie policy (UK)
This Cookie Policy was last updated on 28th June 2020 and applies to citizens of the United Kingdom.1. IntroductionOur website, https://dawngibbins.com (hereinafter: “the website”) uses cookies and other related technologies (for convenience all technologies are referred to as “cookies”). Cookies are also placed by third parties we have engaged. In the document below we inform you about the use of cookies on our website.2. What are cookies?A cookie is a small simple file that is sent along with pages of this website and stored by your browser on the hard drive of your computer or another device. The information stored therein may be returned to our servers or to the servers of the relevant third parties during a subsequent visit.3. What are scripts?A script is a piece of programme code that is used to make our website function properly and interactively. This code is executed on our server or on your device.4. What is a web beacon?A web beacon (or a pixel tag) is a small, invisible piece of text or image on a website that is used to monitor traffic on a website. In order to do this, various data about you is stored using web beacons.5. ConsentWhen you visit our website for the first time, we will show you a pop-up with an explanation about cookies. As soon as you click on “Accept All cookies”, you consent to us using all cookies and plug-ins as described in the pop-up and this Cookie Policy. You can disable the use of cookies via your browser, but please note that our website may no longer work properly.5.1 Manage your consent settings6. Cookies6.1 Technical or functional cookiesSome cookies ensure that certain parts of the website work properly and that your user preferences remain known. By placing functional cookies, we make it easier for you to visit our website. This way, you do not need to repeatedly enter the same information when visiting our website and, for example, the items remain in your shopping cart until you have paid. We may place these cookies without your consent.6.2 Advertising cookiesOn this website we use advertising cookies, enabling us to gain insights into the campaign results. This happens based on a profile we create based on your behavior on https://dawngibbins.com. With these cookies you, as website visitor are linked to a unique ID, but will not profile your behavior and interests to serve personalized ads.Because these cookies are marked as tracking cookies, we ask your permission to place these.6.3 Social media buttonsOn our website we have included buttons for Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram and Pinterest to promote webpages (e.g. “like”, “pin”) or share (e.g. “tweet”) on social networks like Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram and Pinterest. These buttons work using pieces of code coming from Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram and Pinterest themselves. This code places cookies. These social media buttons also can store and process certain information, so a personalized advertisement can be shown to you.Please read the privacy statement of these social networks (which can change regularly) to read what they do with your (personal) data which they process using these cookies. The data that is retrieved is anonymized as much as possible. Facebook, Twitter, LinkedIn, Instagram and Pinterest are located in the United States.7. Placed cookiesGoogle Analytics
We use Google Analytics for website statistics. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Statistics (anonymous)
_ga
2 years
_gid
1 day
Count and track pageviews
Statistics
_gat_gtag_UA_*
1 minute
Store a unique user ID
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Analytics Privacy Statement.
Facebook
We use Facebook for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
_fbp
3 months
Store and track visits across websites
actppresence
Sharing
For more information, please read the Facebook Privacy Statement.
Divi (Elegant Themes)
Name
Retention
Function
Functional
et-pb-recent-items-colors
persistent
Provide functions across pages
et-pb-recent-items-font_family
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.
ET Editor
Name
Retention
Function
Purpose pending investigation
et-editor-available-post-*
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.
WooCommerce
Name
Retention
Function
Functional
wc_cart_hash_*
session
Store items in shopping cart
wc_fragments_*
persistent
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.
Automattic
Name
Retention
Function
Statistics
tk_ai
session
Store a unique user ID
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.
Google Fonts
We use Google Fonts for display of webfonts. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
Google Fonts API
none
Request user IP address
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google Fonts Privacy Statement.
Google reCAPTCHA
We use Google reCAPTCHA for spam prevention. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
rc::c
session
Sharing
For more information, please read the Google reCAPTCHA Privacy Statement.
Twitter
We use Twitter for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Functional
local_storage_support_test
persistent
Load balancing functionality
Marketing/Tracking
metrics_token
persistent
Store if the user has seen embedded content
Sharing
For more information, please read the Twitter Privacy Statement.
LinkedIn
We use LinkedIn for display of recent social posts and/or social share buttons. Read more
Name
Retention
Function
Marketing/Tracking
bcookie
2 years
Store browser details
li-oatml
Sharing
For more information, please read the LinkedIn Privacy Statement.
Miscellaneous
Name
Retention
Function
Purpose pending investigation
nextendsession
bid_1_password_protected_auth
et_builder_product_version
Sharing
This data is not shared with third parties.
8. Your rights with respect to personal dataYou have the following rights with respect to your personal data:
You have the right to know why your personal data is needed, what will happen to it, and how long it will be retained for.
Right of access: You have the right to access your personal data that is known to us.
Right to rectification: you have the right to supplement, correct, have deleted or blocked your personal data whenever you wish.
If you give us your consent to process your data, you have the right to revoke that consent and to have your personal data deleted.
Right to transfer your data: you have the right to request all your personal data from the controller and transfer it in its entirety to another controller.
Right to object: you may object to the processing of your data. We comply with this, unless there are justified grounds for processing.
To exercise these rights, please contact us. Please refer to the contact details at the bottom of this Cookie Policy. If you have a complaint about how we handle your data, we would like to hear from you, but you also have the right to submit a complaint to the supervisory authority (the Information Commissioner’s Office (ICO)).9. Enabling/disabling and deleting cookiesYou can use your internet browser to automatically or manually delete cookies. You can also specify that certain cookies may not be placed. Another option is to change the settings of your internet browser so that you receive a message each time a cookie is placed. For more information about these options, please refer to the instructions in the Help section of your browser.Please note that our website may not work properly if all cookies are disabled. If you do delete the cookies in your browser, they will be placed again after your consent when you visit our websites again.10. Contact detailsFor questions and/or comments about our Cookie Policy and this statement, please contact us by using the following contact details:Healthy Happy Hub Ltd
Heather Bank Farm
Congleton Edge Road
Congleton
United Kingdom
Website: https://dawngibbins.com
Email: data@lifewishes.co.uk
This Cookie Policy was synchronised with cookiedatabase.org on 28th June 2020
Search for:
Cookie policy (UK)
Site by mcm2
FollowFollowFollowFollowFollow
